<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Silverman Lab</title>
    <link>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Silverman Lab</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>publications</title>
      <link>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/publications/</guid>
      <description>preprints A Statistical Analysis of Compositional Surveys. arXiv
Microbiota responses to different prebiotics are conserved within individuals and associated with habitual fiber intake. bioRxiv
2022 Multiomics implicate gut microbiota in altered lipid and energy metabolism in Parkinson’s disease. NPJ Parkinsson&amp;rsquo;s Disease
2021 Scalable estimation of microbial co-occurrence networks with Variational Autoencoders. NeurIPS
Bayesian Multinomial Logistic Normal Models through Marginally Latent Matrix-T Processes. Journal of Machine Learning Resarch (Accepted)
Measuring and Mitigating PCR Bias in Microbiome Data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>code</title>
      <link>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/code/</guid>
      <description>fido Bayesian multinomial logistic normal models, really fast. Lots of models including linear and non-linear regression, time-series analysis, and joint modeling of multi-omic data. renamed from stray. GitHub
RcppHungarian Header library and R functions to solve minimum cost bipartite matching problem using Huhn-Munkres algorithm. CRAN
RcppCoDA Blazing fast library for the analysis of compositional data with both C++ and R interfaces GitHub
philr Phylogenetic partitioning based ILR transform for metagenomics data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>open positions</title>
      <link>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/positions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/positions/</guid>
      <description>We are currently hiring graduate students. Contact Justin Silverman if you are interested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>press</title>
      <link>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/press/</guid>
      <description>Footprints of the invisible enemy – Why a study showing that COVID-19 is everywhere is good news. (April 2020). The Economist
How deadly is the coronavirus? The true fatality rate is tricky to find, but researchers are getting close. (July 2020) The Conversation
New Study Suggests 8.7 million Americans had Coronavirus in March but 80% were never diagnosed. (June 22, 2020). CNN with Wolf Blitzer and Sanjay Gupta
Study Identifies Abnormal Surge of Flu-like illness in March.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jsilve24.github.io/SilvermanLab/research/</guid>
      <description>in brief We conduct cutting-edge research developing Bayesian statistical and machine learning methods for the analysis of various types of data including genomic, electronic health, and public health data.
Our lab is founded on collaborations with both accademia and industry, please contact us if you are interested in potential collaboration.
long form If it has cool math and an impactful question, we are interested. Based on Dr. Silverman&amp;rsquo;s combined medical and statistical training, we tend to gravitate to problems in the analysis of biomedical data; especially, genomics and electronic health data.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
